Call an ambulance!
Now you see why I
didn't call an ambulance.
I want back in the game.
This could actually work.
These contacts are comfortable with me.
You show up. start asking
questions. they'll get nervous.
You said that there was
no one here besides you
- when Logan OD'd. right?
- That's right.
You pull it off. we'll
bring you on full-time.
- Front me a key.
- You got one day to bring me $12.000.
Buy this key. and I will
bring you another one tomorrow.
You wanna talk to your daddy?
Just drive the fucking car.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Alejandro! Alejandro!
- Synced and corrected by javiernv -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Good morning.
After the meeting.
we have to find a new stash house.
What's wrong with this one?
Uh. it's too understated.
I'd like to find something flashier.
We have two deals to make today.
weapons arriving tomorrow.
We don't have time to...
This isn't a discussion.
We're out of here after
the meeting tonight.
You should have a bump.
I'm serious. Straighten you right out.
I don't think showing up
high to Avi Benhamou's house
would be strategically sound.
Well. like. I said. I don't
think you should show up at all.
All right. look. I
gotta run some errands.
So wait an hour. pack up
the rest. and then. uh.
meet me at that parking garage
on Sunset. behind Carney's.
Where are you going?
You know what place I mean?
Yellow train?
One hour.
You're late.
You have my cash?
Fuck is this?
I sent you in there to take
money. not family photos.
Where is it. Oso? Mm?
I'll give you the
money when I feel safe.
Safe from what?
The kind of man who
steals from his own father.
Gustavo. we weren't
stealing the money...
Pedro! Pedro. put the gun down.
- Stop it! You want the money?
- Yeah. I want the fucking money.
If you kill him. we're
never gonna see it.
I'm not gonna kill him.
I'm gonna put holes in
him until he gives it up.
Pedro. look at me. Can you
come talk to me. please? Please.
Pedro. Pedro. look at me.
Stop. Put the gun down.
What are you doing?
He's fucking threatening us.
We've had this
conversation. I know.
Yeah. So what?
Get in your car and go.
You're never gonna get...
Just get in.
Okay. Fine.
You sure you got this?
Yes. Just go.
Yeah. whatever.
Ahh. You didn't even think to call...
Give me a heads up?
- You said you don't have a phone.
- Of course I have a phone.
It's not that I don't have a phone.
It's just that I don't like
talking business over the phone.
You know why?
Someone could be listening?
- And then what happens?
- You get caught.
- And then what?
- You go to jail.
No. you go to fucking prison.
So I don't want you to call.
I want you to do things exactly the
way we said they would be done...
so you don't have to call.
- Uh. I'm sorry. What was that?
- What?
That noise.
What the fuck?!
Strip.
I was told you didn't want to be known.
"Alejandro. I wanna meet your partner."
"No. Avi. you cannot meet my partner.
My partner doesn't wanna be met."
I say. "Okay. Alejandro here...
"He parties. He's legit.
He makes me feel safe and
warm and fuzzy inside."
But then. first deal...
You show up. all nifty and shifty.
And nervous.
Okay. so I... if I'm shifty.
it's 'cause it sounds like
there's somebody
giving birth back there.
And you're trying to
get me naked at gunpoint.
So I know you wear no
wire in your ass crack.
Listen. if it makes you feel
any better. we'll all strip.
And then we're gonna sit
here like a bunch of faggots
while you explain why you
suddenly need to be here
to conduct our business.
Take off your clothes. everybody.
What are you waiting for?
All right. Come on!
Turn around. Show me your ass.
Show me your fucking ass!
Avi!
What happened to him?
Do you see how dark that is?
That means that he's
bleeding internally.
- So now you're a fucking doctor?!
- No. He needs one.
Don't worry about it!
Just be quiet
Get the fuck outta here!
- I... We need to make this deal. Avi.
- No. fuck!
We need to make this deal.
Avi. When should we come back?
I'll call you.
Get out!
¿Aquí entrenas también?
Mm-hmm.
That's quite the smell.
¿Qué quieres saber. Gustavo?
Todo.
I don't have that kind of
time. Wanna be more specific?
Órale.
Who did I kill?
Se llamaba Max
And he works for Ramiro. Pedro's father.
Did you and Pedro set me up?
- Why would we do that?
- I don't know.
Why would Pedro rob his own father?
I already told you. Oso. We
weren't stealing the money.
The plan was to
borrow it. flip the product.
put it back before Ramiro
ever knew it was missing.
What product? Hmm?
Not marijuana.
You know. Pedro told
me you didn't talk much.
Was he wrong. or do I just
bring something out of you?
We said if you pulled this off.
we'd bring you on full-time.
- And even though you fucked up. that...
- I fucked up?
That offer still stands.
I fucked up. Lucía?
Oso. I'm gonna give you
access to everything.
Our suppliers. our
stash house. our product.
Pero necesito ese dinero.
You'd betray your own family for money?
¿Por qué?
Gustavo..
No te pago pa' que andes platicando.
Quit.
- I can't.
- Tell him you quit.
In two months. you can buy this place.
let anyone you want train for free.
You'll be a hero.
Hello?
Yuda...
- Yuda.
- The door was unlocked.
Not a good time. Go away.
But I got your money.
- I got your money.
- What?
- What. you actually did it?
- Screw his money now!
Screw your mother. motherfucker!
I can see you in some shit right now.
so if it's all good. I'll
just take a couple keys and go.
- Why? You want more?
- Ain't that how it work?
I do good. I get more opportunity.
Yeah.
But I'm going to need you
to do something for me first.
Okay. so if you get pulled over.
tell 'em that you're... you're
the chauffeur or something.
Use that silver tongue
of yours. All right?
Now whatever happens...
Whatever happens...
I do not want police in this house.
Do you understand?
Uh-huh.
What about the keys?
Nah. I meant the coke.
You want the cocaine
inside the car with you?
I thought you're smarter than this.
Come back after that.
I'll give it to you then...
my Rolls intact.
And. Franklin.
I'm giving you a wondrous
responsibility here...
The chance to save a life.
Don't fuck it up.
Oh. my God. Get a gurney.
I got you.
Why are you intent on
making this harder than it has to be?
That guy's a lunatic. We
shouldn't be doing business with him.
Hey. Hey!
I had him under
control until you showed up.
You know.
things between Logan and I
were working because he trusted me.
Okay.
Stop lying to me.
What is this? I don't know what this is.
It's a woman's earring. I
found it near Logan's body.
Okay. Tell me. what
do you think happened?
I don't know. You...
You told me that you and Logan
were alone when he OD'd. right?
Yeah.
There was blood all over that house.
And then I found this and blonde hair.
So yeah. I'm thinking...
maybe Logan was with a girl...
Or girls... when he OD'd.
Somebody panicked. Maybe they wanted
to call an ambulance or something.
and you did what you thought
you had to do to salvage the op.
You think I killed some girl?
- Do you know how that sounds?
- No. please. tell me.
- Crazy.
- No.
- Paranoid. like you don't know...
- No. No. This is not...
- what's right and what's...
- This is not in my head.
Yes. it is. And you need
to get control of yourself.
because the Mexicans are
coming to the house at 10.
So either show up calm and
clear. ready to make a deal.
or stay away.
I get more than 24 hours this time?
Don't push it.
Just out of curiosity...
Who'd you find to take
off that kilo off your hands?
My fairy godmother.
Smart-ass kid.
Don't get yourself killed on that bike!
Then I'll never see my fucking money!
Boo!
What? Y'all can't say hello?
No. David. what have you done?
I told you never to
come to this house again.
Cut the act.
Nobody can hear us.
'Sup. Aunt Loo?
Hey.
You don't look too good.
You testing my patience. boy.
I should whoop your ass for getting
her involved with this shit.
- He ain't put no gun to my head.
- It won't happen again.
And I ain't even here on all that.
Bought a bike. I can't
leave it at my place.
- You can leave it here.
- You can't leave here.
You see the messes you
bring up in my house?
Had my shit on lock. man.
Jerome... out of pocket bitches
screaming on the front porch.
Who really
bringing the mess here?
Bitch. who is you?
- Who am I?
- Aw. damn. Damn.
Who you poppin'
up in your face for?
- You need to calm down.
- Naw. I ain't calming nothin' down.
Supposed to help her move somebody.
- Hold this for me.
- Don't want her to see my face.
- Y'all here?
- Hold my...
- Hell. no.
- Please...
- Unh-unh. No.
- Y'all here?
What you two doing?
- Nothing.
- Chillin'.
You was gonna stand me up?
Uh. I was just about to come home.
Well. come on then.
You puttin' me behind.
Where's Louie?
She in her room. She
ain't feeling too good.
Probably sick 'cause
you got that motorcycle.
Don't you know that thing
is death on two wheels?
Yeah. I just love 'em too much.
You just love trouble too much.
Tell her I brought her dish
back. Come on. Franklin.
Patty cake. patty cake...
Fine example you settin' for your boy.
kicking old women outta their home.
Teaching him what happens
when you don't pay rent.
Good riddance.
Roaches'd complain if they could.
- The place outta be condemned.
- That's the last of it.
- Suck my titties. boy.
- Hey!
Act right or I'm-a call the Sheriffs.
Can we go now?
You know what? Not yet.
What else you got up there.
Ms. Perkins? Let's go see.
What do you think you're doin'?
Open that grate right there.
Reach in and tell me what you find.
- For real?
- Mm-hmm.
Best not be no rat trap up here.
Oh. there isn't.
What the hell?
You snake.
That ain't mine.
Chicken milk bomb.
Milk and raw chicken
left in the heating duct.
Sit there long enough.
it'd be damn near toxic.
Ain't that right. Ms. Perkins?
- I don't know nothin' about that.
- Uh-huh.
You trippin'.
What is he doing here?
Hi.
Hello.
- Cissy.
- I wasn't expecting you.
And Franklin. What a nice
surprise. Good to see you. son.
So. um. how's it going here?
Um. we're just about done. Sir. Uh. Sir.
That's right.
Let your little house nigga
finish doing your dirty for you.
Hey. I think it's time you
went ahead and got going. Ma'am.
All these years. people
been calling your rich ass.
- Ms. Perkins...
- Leaks. Bad electrical.
- Ms. Perkins. what did I tell you?
- Fucked up plumbing!
I didn't come here to argue with you!
Now you show?! To see me thrown out?!
Well. I ain't going! Just
give us back and get going!
I told you about that.
You shut up! I'm not talking to you!
- Go ahead. Call the Sheriff.
- Ms. Perkins!
Let him see how you got
these people living!
Ma'am. you're trespassing!
You the criminal here!
Ronald. please. let
me handle this. okay?
- Well. then handle it.
- I'm going to.
- I don't want a fucking riot out here.
- Today is to be a day of reckoning!
Oh. my God!
I'm gonna get...
You need to get out right...
Leave!
Come on! Come on now!
Hey. it's McDonald.
Yeah. I'm good. Yeah. listen. um.
I'm looking for a warehouse space.
1.000 square feet minimum
in an industrial area
where trucks coming and going
wouldn't draw too much attention.
And if it's close to
Hawthorne. that would be ideal.
No. I don't... I don't
give a shit about that.
I do need an outside line. though.
Yeah. Uh. 24 hours. Less if you can.
Okay. Yep. Thank you.
That chicken milk bomb...
Woman had an arm on her. too.
I thought she was gonna put
it right through Tulf's window.
Yeah. I wish she had.
Hey. Man signs my
checks. Show some respect.
Stop eatin' my onion rings!
I just wish you didn't have to
deal with those crazy folks all day.
They're not
crazy. just desperate.
Mm.
Can I know why you
were at Jerome's today?
I need a reason to see family?
You know me and my brother
done come a long way.
and I done worked hard to love Louie.
but I don't want you spending
so much time over there.
- Come on. Mom.
- I know you heard it before.
And I also know you're plenty smart.
So you understand if I'm
saying it. I must mean it.
That your way of asking to be excused?
May I be excused?
Mm.
You wanna stop leaving your
things all over the place. baby?
My bad. Thank you.
- What do you have in there any...
- Um...
Oh. come on. Franklin.
Kitchen's only
two steps away. man.
What do you got in that bag?
Nothing.
Hoodie. Henry Ford book. bunch of stuff.
I like reading. too. you know.
Oh. I know you like reading. Henry Ford?
Saw Pops last night.
Where?
On Western.
He all right?
Tough to say.
Thanks for the plates.
Who is this?
Lucía Villanueva.
No te preocupes. todo va a estar bien.
So you bring
this guy in this place?
Besides Pedro. Gustavo's
the most trusted man I have.
You'll be dealing a lot with
him. so I'd be really nice.
- Pasen por aquí. Siéntense.
- Gracias.
So?
Where's Logan?
Uh... there was an
accident a few days ago.
Logan OD'd.
You're telling me Logan's dead?
- Well...
- Hey. You started the party without me.
I'm Reed Thompson. It's nice
to meet you. Ms. Villanueva.
Who the fuck are you.
the replacement white boy?
I. uh. I was a friend of Logan's.
He never mentioned you.
Yeah. I asked to be a silent partner.
So obviously. things have changed.
I was told to expect Pedro.
But from everything
I've heard about Pedro.
you don't seem like... Pedro.
Gustavo.
Okay.
Gustavo. Uh. it's nice to meet you.
- Uh. would you care for a drink?
- No.
Okay. Uh. again.
I'm... I'm very. very sorry about Logan.
I know that this must come as a shock.
Are you gonna use Logan's death
as an excuse to fuck with me
and change the terms of our arrangement?
No.
Are you gonna act like an asshole
and be difficult to deal with?
W... Uh... Well. no. I
mean. I hadn't planned on it.
Then you have nothing to be sorry for.
Can we get on with this deal?
And the money?
You wanna count it?
Not if you say we don't have to.
You wanna sample the product?
Two weeks...
you'll be ready to
purchase another 25 keys?
No problem.
We'll be in contact then.
It is nice to meet you.
You. too. Oso.
Both of you.
So. uh. what do you know about her?
I know that she can pay.
which is all that I care about.
Okay. I. uh. I found
us a new stash house.
It's closer to Hawthorne. So that's
where we're gonna do business from now on.
Count that. I'll be back
with the other half soon.
Oh. wait. wait. wait.
You're going to Avi's? Alone?
How you think that's going to work?
This way.
Pásale. Cierra la puerta.
Bienvenido.
¿Listas para jalar?
- Sí.
- Uh-huh...
Síganme.
Las bolsas ahí en la mesa.
Señoras. por favor. desnudense.
La ropa.
Cada una en una silla.
25 kilos. Roughly 55 pounds.
880 ounces.
25.000 grams.
Cut modestly. still purer than
anything coming over the border.
And at $100 a gram. a
better value as well.
Dealers get 10%.
processors $1.000 a day
to buy silence and loyalty.
Chunk goes to the church and
other miscellaneous expenditures...
Plastic bags. rubber bands.
scales. cash counters. fuel.
bribes for doormen. club managers.
bartenders. concierges.
Budgeted out at $10.000 a load.
There will also be
breakage. free samples.
Conservatively. another 50
to 100 grams per shipment.
After all expenses.
Oso. those 25 kilos could net
us just under $2.1 million.
Where have you been?
I was trying your place. I
couldn't get ahold of you.
I've been with my father all
day. trying to keep him calm.
Guess it went smooth?
Mostly. You're not gonna
believe what happened to Logan.
Tell me on the way.
They called a meeting.
They're wondering where you've been.
Ya. está bien por hoy. Venganse mañana
No. no. no. Sigan trabajando.
Gustavo can watch them.
¿Verdad?
Órale.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Ahí te dejo.
Okay. okay. put the money.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Put the money!
Okay. okay. okay!
Wah!
Ahh! Ohh!
- Oh. you came back.
- How's your man doing?
- Apparently. he'll live.
- Wow. That's good to hear.
So what now?
You apologize? You
beg for my forgiveness?
Tell me your life story so
I believe that you're legit?
No. this is the part
where I tell you that. uh.
we're not doing business together.
But good luck to you.
Stop.
What. you...
don't wanna do business with me?
Look. I am a simple. reasonable man.
I just wanna do business with
other simple. reasonable men.
- I'm a simple. reasonable man.
- Wait. You're a lunatic.
- I'm eccentric.
- You're paranoid.
I'm cautious. Okay.
so... you didn't frisk me.
You didn't ask me a single question.
You stuck a gun in my
face and you told me
your were gonna shoot me
unless I stripped naked.
You got me nervous. I
didn't know who you are.
Besides. it's a lot of product
we're talking about here.
Okay. So if you're feeling nervous.
what we do is we sit down
and we talk things through.
like adults. which I'd
have been happy to do.
But what you don't do
is put a gun in my face
and tell me you're gonna
shoot me unless I get naked.
Mm.
Well. I'm trying to apologize
here. but you rub it in my face.
- Now who's unreasonable?
- No. no. you haven't apologized.
I'm sorry.
I still don't trust you.
See. I think you still got
some of that Louis XIII left.
So why don't you pour us both a drink?
We'll sit down and we'll
talk things through.
see if we can't come
to some understanding.
And if we can. we'll
do business together.
If we can't. I'll take
my product elsewhere.
No hard feelings.
Cool?
Number 48.
chili burger with fries.
Number 53. fish and chips.
Franklin!
See y'all.
So. um. you're just. like.
sneaking out every night now. huh?
Daddy's working the night shift.
And you're welcome to
come hang out if you want.
Uh. don't he check on you sometime?
- Sometimes.
- Then I'm good.
- You really scared of him. huh?
- Hell. yeah! Man.
You didn't used to be.
Yeah. that was when we was kids.
But then you got fine.
and he got psycho.
You think I'm fine?
And it's 'cause
of that you scared of him?
Not 'cause you selling weed now?
Pssh! What? I ain't selling no weed.
Come on. Franklin. You think I'm
a fool? That I don't see things?
I don't know what you think you see.
but I ain't slingin' no weed.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
What is that?
Nothin'.
- Where you get it?
- Go home. Mel.
- Come on. Franklin.
- Go home.
For real.
Derek. what's the best
part of working with your wife?
Well. you always know who's worst.
Vamos.
- Hi. Tío.
- Where were you?
Ramiro.
21 años ya he tenido este negocio
con mi hermano. ¿verdad?
21 años. Y en ese tiempo yo no he
tenido ninguna traición... Una traición
como esta. que ha sido ¡en mi casa!
IEn mi casa!
El responsable sabía lo que estaba
haciendo. y donde estaba el dinero.
Y esa lista es muy corta e incluye
a varios de ustedes aquí.
Mi hijo tiene esta idea que fue
Max que vino... con un amigo.
Y cuando se robaron todo.
mató a Max y se fue.
This is Javier. Hermano de Max.
Dice que no tiene idea quien
ayudó y traicionó a Max.
Si no encuentran mi dinero en una semana...
Voy a empezar a investigar
a cada uno de ustedes.
¿Entienden?
Muchas gracias.
What a mess.
You think Ramiro's right? About Max?
The truth always comes out.
What concerns me is how much damage
Ramiro will do in the meantime.
¿Necesitas un abrigo?
Oh. no. no. no. I'm
fine. How are you feeling?
Well... Your mother says I'm too skinny.
All those years on my
ass about my weight.
and now I need to put some on.
She just wants to help you.
¿Todavía disfrutas de este trabajo?
¿Eres feliz?
Sí. Papá.
Come have dinner at the ranch this week.
Tu mamá te extraña.
¿Mi mamá o tú?
Te quiero.
Your father's lost his fucking mind.
Yeah. that's what I
was trying to tell you.
I mean. since when does he toss bodies
across his fucking living room floor?
I can't believe you're
smoking this shit right now.
We just have to patient. okay?
Start the coke business up slow.
He's not gonna stop until
he knows who did this.
We can't just wait
around for him to kill us.
You really think he'd do that?
Hey!
Uhh! Look here!
Well. I guess you ain't no one
hit wonder after all. is you?
I got tracks for days.
Just say the word.
Let me tell you somethin'
about me. Franklin.
I ain't about that powder.
That is just a necessary
experience that I provide.
which makes my place so special.
Of course.
Get him $30.000.
Hold up. We said $16.000 per.
Well. I thought we'd start
with a nice round number first.
I'm sure there's something
we can offer you here
that. uh. will ensure that you
leave here feeling taken care of.
- I'm afraid there ain't.
- No?
Mm.
Oh. you 'bout that money. huh?
All right then. Get him his money.
Thank you.
How's your auntie?
She staying in tonight?
I can't imagine she felt
too welcome after last time.
Well. she had that shit coming for days.
Well. you also held a gun to my chin.
Oh. you sensitive.
I'm hoping this is the beginning
of a long. fruitful business
relationship. Claudia.
I don't think it's too
much to ask for the words
"My fault" followed by
"Shit won't happen again."
Your showing your youth up in here. boy.
And you showing me you're too
proud to admit you're wrong.
Excuse me.
Everything all right?
Yep.
It's a shame you can't stick around.
Bitches love the Candyman.
Hit me one more time!
Uhh! Good God.
Hey. who are you with?
- Whatchu mean?
- You slow. nigga?
This shit seem like jokes
to you? Who you with?
Ain't with nobody. I'm with me.
So you thought it was okay
to slide up here and steal
our best customer?!
Shut the fuck up!
Shut up!
Aah!
Yeah.
Hey. Don't waste no bullets
on that bitch-ass nigga.
We got the bag.
Not yet.
This ain't Mayberry. bitch.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today